I said，「Look，lady，the seats haven't gotten smaller，
我说：小姐 座椅没变小
your ass has gotten bigger.「
是你的屁股变大了
I'm sorry，sir。This cabin is restricted to first class.
抱歉 先生 这是头等舱
Are you looking for this？
你要看这个吗？
Can I get you anything？
您需要喝点什么？
Scotch。Blended。Straight.
威士忌 不加冰
This is your captain speaking.
各位女士先生 我是机长
We've got a report of some turbulence ahead.
前方有乱流
Please return to your seats and fasten your seat belts…
请回座并系紧安全带
and remain there until we release the fasten-seat-belt sign.
直至系安全带的灯号熄灭为止
I hear birds can't fly this high.
我听说鸟飞不到这个高度
I hear only angels can.
我听说只有天使能
Where's the bomb？
炸弹呢？
I am the bomb.
我就是炸弹
- Shall I pour your Scotch？-No，I'll take the bottle.
- 需要我帮你倒酒吗？-不 我直接喝
Another movie from an old TV show.
又是旧剧集改编的电影
What are you gonna do？
你打算怎么办？
Walk out.
离开
Very funny.
真好笑
No，it isn't.
不 不好笑
What are you doing？！
你干嘛？
What are you doing？！Get off of me！
你干嘛？放开我
Help me！Help me！
救命 救命
Help me！Be careful！
救命 小心啊
Nice flight？
飞行愉快吗？
You crazy bastard！
你这个疯子
I think you mean 「crazy bitch.」
你是说「疯女人」吧
What is this？What's going on here？
这是什么？这是怎么回事？
Damn，I hate to fly.
妈的 我讨厌飞行
No way！No way！
不可能 不可能
What's with that？！Who are you people？！
怎么回事？你们是谁？
Who are you people？！
你们到底是谁？
Once upon a time，there were three very different little girls
从前 有三个很不一样的女孩
who grew up to be three very different women.
长成了三个与众不同的女人
Making her a five-day champion。Way to go，Natalie.
她蝉连了五天的冠军宝座 干的好 娜妲莉
They have three things in common：They're brilliant，beautiful…
她们的共同点是 聪明 美丽
I'm going to be all over you！
我会盯着你
You will be kissing my ass…
让你吃足苦头
and they work for me.
她们也为我效力
My name is Charlie.
我是查理
- Let's go this way。-No！
- 往这边走 - 不
This way！
往这边
Wait。I'm not a yo-yo！
等等 这又不是拔河
《霹雳娇娃》
∮ 叫我晨曦天使吧 宝贝 ∮
∮ 在你走之前 轻抚我脸颊 ∮
Good morning，Starfish.
早安 小海星
Good morning，Chad.
早安 查德
Sweet Chad.
甜蜜的查德
I figured we could have a little breakfast.
我想我们可以吃点早餐
And then，maybe，after，
然后 也许
we could have a little Chad.
我们可以做个小查德
Hold that thought.
暂停一下
Yes，I'll be right in.
好 我马上到
Isn't that just the luck？
真是不巧
I can make something besides eggs.
我不是只会煎蛋
No，it's not the eggs.
不是蛋的关系
Is it the boat？
是船的关系？
It's not the boat。I have to go.
也不是船的关系 我得走了
Is it the Chad？
是查德的关系？
It might be the Chad.
有可能
It's the Chad… the Chad！
是查德的关系
Eduardo，move me.
小艾 放音乐
Good morning.
早安
You know I signed the waiver，so feel free to stick things in my slot.
我签过免签收同意书 把东西从洞里塞进来就好
Thanks.
谢谢
No problem.
没什么
Hey！I'll be right in.
我马上到
I want to get one thing straight between us.
我想说清楚一件事
Go ahead。We're past keeping secrets at this point.
说吧 我们之间早无秘密
This is going to be long…
这玩意很长
hard and rough.
又硬又难搞
Sometimes when it's rough，I just get there faster.
有时越难搞 我就能越快搞定
If you don't defuse this bomb，L.A。will be an underwater attraction.
你若不能拆除这枚炸弹 洛杉矶就会沉入海底
Which wire？The red one or the blue one？
哪跟电线？红的还是蓝的？
That is not helping.
那样没用
My muffins.
我的小松糕
This is stupid，anyway。Why wouldn't I just yank the wire？
这真蠢 我为何不能干脆拉掉电线？
They're dummy wires，honey。The real mechanism is inside.
电线只是掩饰 里面才是重点
Trip the external feedback circuit，the bomb will detonate.
触动反馈线路 炸弹就会爆炸
For a bikini waxer，you know a lot about bombs.
身为除毛师 你还真懂炸弹
Isn't it amazing how much information you can learn off the Internet？
网路能得到的讯息真多 对吧？
I'll be right there.
我马上到
When do I get to meet this Charlie？
我何时能见见这个查理？
Charlie's not a very social person.
查理不喜欢热闹
But Charlie's a chick though，right？
查理是女的 对吧？
I mean，definitely a woman，right？
一定是女的吧？
I can't keep up this fa？ade with Jason anymore.
我无法再对杰森掩饰了
Who wants a man who's intimidated by a strong woman？
谁想要被女强人威胁的男人？
They come on nice until they find out I can shatter a block with my head.
他们发现我能一头撞破砖头之前 总是很多情
I love that trick.
我喜欢那招
Blueberry muffins.
蓝莓小松糕
I made them from scratch.
我照食谱做的
Yum.
好棒
Sounds good.
真不错
These look great，Alex.
看起来真好吃 艾莉丝
Oh，my God.
我的老天
What's this？
这是什么？
Chinese fighting muffin.
中国功夫小松糕
Nothing to laugh about.
没什么好笑的
My buddy took a fighting muffin in the chest，
我朋友被功夫小松糕打中
went home in four Ziploc bags.
结果被装成四袋送回老家
They're not Chinese。They're not fighting。They're blueberry.
它们不是中国人也不会功夫 它们是蓝莓口味的
Are you okay？
你还好吧？
She's having secret-identity trouble.
她有秘密身分的问题
Aren't we all？
我们不都有吗？
Scoot.
坐过去
Alex…
艾莉丝
all my Angels…
我的天使们
the heart is a muscle.
心脏是肌肉组成的
In bodybuilding，we exercise the muscle
在健身时 我们锻炼肌肉
and it grows bigger and stronger.
它就会变大变壮
It's the same with the heart.
心脏也是一样
I must have the heart of a rhino.
我一定有颗犀牛般的心脏
You do。And you'll be proud of it.
没错 要引以为傲
Mes Anges…
我的天使们
these little hurts will heal.
这些小伤会痊愈的
And at crunch time，your hearts will be so buff…
在紧要关头 你的心脏会很强壮
you'll be able to clean and jerk his love…
你将能承接住他的爱
three sets，10 reps each.
三个人都一样
Thanks，Bos.
谢了 老波
Excuse me。I have to take a phone call.
抱歉 我要接个电话
Good morning，Angels.
早安 天使们
Good morning，Charlie.
早安 查理
Dylan，Alex，Natalie，I hope you're ready for your next assignment.
狄纶 艾莉丝 娜妲莉 准备好执行下一个任务了吧
Meet Eric Knox，a brilliant engineer and founder of Knox Technologies
这是艾瑞·诺 天才工程师与诺氏科技创始人
an up-and-coming communications software company.
即将推出尖端的通讯软体
Last night，Knox was kidnapped
昨晚 诺被绑架了
and his voice-identification software was stolen.
他的语音辨识软体也被窃
Who's the lady left behind？
那女士是谁？
Vivian Wood，she is the president of Knox Technologies.
伍·薇安 诺氏科技总裁
Oh，she did it.
是她干的
I guess we can all go home then.
那我们就都可以回家了
Angels，meet Vivian Wood，our new client.
天使们 这是伍·薇安 我们的新客户
She's hired us to find Eric Knox.
她雇请我们去找艾瑞·诺
Hello.
你好
Ms。Wood，Who'd have the most to gain from Knox's disappearance？
诺失踪对谁最有利？
Me，probably。I'm his partner.
也许是我 我是他的伙伴
Before we were partners
在我们成为伙伴之前
we were friends.
我们是朋友
Does Knox have any enemies？
诺有仇家吗？
Roger Corwin。He's owner
罗杰·柯 他是
of Red Star，the largest communications satellite firm.
世上最大的通讯卫星公司「红星」的老板
Six months ago，he tried to buy Knox Technologies.
六个月前 他想买下诺氏科技
When Knox refused to sell，Corwin lost it.
诺拒绝出售 姓柯的气坏了
Charming.
真有趣
Was there a ransom demand？
有要求赎金吗？
Nothing。But I know he's still alive.
没有 但我知道他还活着
I'll study the garage footage。Something may be there.
我研究录影带 也许有线索
So Corwin is our only lead。Hopefully，he'll take us to Knox.
姓柯的是头号嫌犯 希望他能带我们找到诺
Corwin gets a weekly massage at Madame Wong's House of Blossoms.
姓柯的每周都会去马杀鸡
That's our chance to feel him out.
这是我们摸他老底的机会
He said what？
他说什么？
「Over my dead body」？
除非他死？
I can accept those terms.
这倒可以考虑
It's getting a little chilly in here，Yoko。I could use some warming up.
有点冷了 阳子 帮我暖暖身子吧
At your service.
悉听尊便
Good.
很好
Could we get started this millennium？
可以在这世纪内开始吗？
Banzai！
万岁！
Oh yeah.
好爽
You're holding a lot of tension…
你积压太多压力
in your 4th and 5th vertebrae.
在第四第五节脊椎里
I know.
我知道
Let me see if I can work that…
我看看能不能把它
out.
纾解掉
Just by activating the right energy points，you can increase circulation…
只要活化正确的穴道 就能增进血液循环
alleviate pain…
缓解疼痛
or even…
甚至
render a man unconscious.
让人昏迷
Okay，let's go.
好了 动手吧
Palm Pilot.
电子记事簿
Got the car key.
车钥匙复制好了
I got his schedule.
（下载中）
行程表到手了
You must have dozed off.
你一定是睡着了
You're very good
你的双手
with your hands.
真棒
I could use someone like you on my staff.
你可以来我旗下做事
Thanks for the offer，but my hands aren't going anywhere near your staff.
谢谢抬举 但我的手不想接近你的旗下
If Corwin is behind Knox's disappearance
要是姓柯的是诺绑架案的主谋
someone else is doing his dirty work.
一定要有人帮他动手
How's it coming with the kidnapping footage？
录影带有何线索？
I'm enhancing a reflection from the car window.
我在强化车窗上反映的影像
May I take your order？
需要点些什么？
Three cheeseburgers，three french fries and three cherry pies.
三个吉士汉堡 三份薯条 还有三个樱桃派
What do you guys want？
你们要吃什么？
Here's one of the kidnappers.
这是其中一个绑匪
Creepy Thin Man.
一个竹竿怪人
Now we just look for him.
现在我们只要找他
And see if he works for Corwin.
看他是否是姓柯的手下
What's Corwin doing tonight？
姓柯的今晚要做什么？
Who's up for crashing a party？
谁想突袭派对啊？
Bos.
老波
- Thanks，Nat。-No problem.
- 谢了 小娜 - 没问题
It's a mic-transmitter。Put it on your back molar.
这是微波传送器 放在臼齿后
I know。It's a mouth-mic.
我知道 这是口内麦克风
We'll be able to always stay in touch.
我们可以保持联系
We're in deep cover now，so if…
我们现在从事秘密任务
you can't remember John David，just call me J.D.Think of…
你们若不记得我叫约翰·戴维 就叫我小戴 就像…
- Jelly doughnut。-Jack Daniel's.
- 小呆 - 小待
- Juvenile delinquents。-John DeLorean.
- 小黛 - 小袋
There's your date，J.D.
你的对象来了 小戴
Excuse me，ladies.
失陪一下 女士们
Roger Corwin。Welcome.
我是罗杰·柯 欢迎
John David Rage，self-help guru.
约翰·大戴 自学导师
John David Rage？
约翰·大戴？
Relax，Bos。Order a drink.
放轻松点 要杯饮料吧
Excuse me。Miss？
抱歉 小姐？
- Hi。-Hi，miss.
- 嗨 - 小姐
- A hammerhead，please。-No problem.
- 请给我来杯调酒 - 没问题
Any creepy thin men？
有看到竹竿怪人吗？
Lots of creepy，none thin.
很多怪人 但都不瘦
- I was wondering if… - No.
- 我想… - 不
- So there's no chance… - No。No.
- 那就是没机会… - 没
That's incredible.
真不可思议
What is？
什么？
Your smile.
你的笑容
Thanks.
谢了
This place，it's Japanese，is it not？
这是日式庭园 对吧？
It's a 13th-century Shinto temple.
这是13世纪的神社
I had it…
我是用…
I had it FedEx'd from Kyoto.
我是用快递从京都寄过来的
Blowfish？
河豚？
Isn't that poisonous？
那不是有毒吗？
It's a rare delicacy for the man who has no fear of an excruciating death.
这是男人的珍馐 尤其是对那种大无畏的男人
Technically，1 in 60 is fatal.
被毒死的机率有六十分之一
Tastes like chicken.
尝起来很像鸡肉
That would go very nicely with broccoli.
跟甘蓝菜煮会很配
The man laughs at death.
这人嘲笑死神呢
Good work，Bos。Get him to talk about Knox.
干的好 快让他谈谈诺
At last，a worthy adversary.
值得尊敬的对手
But let's see if you can survive a test of intuition and judgment.
来测试你的直觉与判断力吧
Nat，that bartender is cute.
小娜 那酒保很可爱呢
I'm working.
我在工作
He likes you。Go back and flirt a little.
他喜欢你 回去再调个情吧
That was fast.
真快啊
I'm not called Balls-Out Natalie for nothing.
我叫大胆娜妲莉并非浪得虚名
Right.
是啊
I never saw you working here before.
我没看过你在这里工作
I'm new。I'm like a virgin。I mean，it's my first time
我是新来的 我就像个处女 这是我第一次…
here at Corwin's.
来柯氏旗下工作
Oh，boy。She's going down.
天啊 她搞砸了
No way。He's into her.
不可能 他喜欢她
Just pick up the tray and walk away.
拿起托盘 走开
No，no。Stay。Stay and talk to him.
不… 留下来跟他说话
- Flip your hair。-What？
- 甩头发 - 什么？
Flip your goddamn hair.
快甩你的头发
Excuse me，I'm sorry。I don't usually do this，but I was wondering…
抱歉 我不常如此 但我想…
unless you're already seeing someone else.
除非你已有男朋友
- Yeah。-Of course you are，sorry.
- 是啊 - 当然啰
No！I'm not seeing anyone.
不 我没有男朋友
Free.
我有空
Okay，Thursday？
好 星期四？
My favorite day.
我最喜欢的日子
Great。I'll get tickets.
很好 我去弄票
I love tickets.
我爱死票了
What do you know？A guy who speaks Natalie.
真有趣 有人跟娜妲莉约会呢
Where's J.D.？
小戴呢？
Will somebody help me up，please？
来个人帮帮我吧？
Hello，girls？Are you hearing me？
女孩们 你们听见了吗？
Thin Man，10 o'clock.
竹竿人 十点钟方向
Why do they always run？
他们为什么老爱落跑？
Watch it！
小心
Nat！
娜妲莉
- Brace！-Jump！
- 架手桥 - 跳
Check them all！
一一检查
- Clear！-Clear！
- 没问题 - 没问题
Clear！
没问题
Knox.
诺
Great work，Angels，but our job's only half-finished.
干的好 天使们 但任务只完成一半
There's still the matter of Mr.Knox's stolen technology.
还有诺先生被窃的先进技术
What's so special about your software？
你的软体有何特别？
It's really…It's really quite amazing.
它很惊人
We developed a program。You see，everyone's voice is unique.
我们发展了一个程式 每个人的声音都很独特
It has a unique signature…
它有独特的特性
like a snowflake。And it can be mapped…
跟雪花一样 它能被描画
It's audio DNA.
那是声音的DNA
It makes it impossible to disguise or scramble a voice signal.
它让别人无法假造音纹
Which is why Corwin wants it.
所以姓柯的才会想要它
Of course。All Red Star's satellites have global positioning systems.
当然 红星的卫星都有 全球定位系统
Combine that with voice identification.
若结合了声音辨识
Any cell phone could be a homing device.
每只手机都会是自动导引装置
No one could hide.
无人能躲藏
Imagine how dangerous this would be in the wrong hands.
想想这要是被误用会有多危险
The end of privacy.
隐私权不再
That's where you come in，Angels.
天使们 注意听了
Corwin is premiering his Red Star racer at the California Speedway.
姓柯的赛车队将在赛车场亮相
Our chance to plant a hidden camera on Corwin.
藉机去他车上装针孔摄影机
Looks like it's off to the races，Angels.
看来你们该加足马力了
When Roger Corwin first got involved in the world of racing…
当柯罗杰首度参与世界赛车时
a lot of people said it was a stopgap for my waning libido.
许多人说 我是因性欲减退才来玩车
I had them all fired.
我把他们都解雇了
What's so funny？I did.
有什么好笑的？是真的
Thanks for coming to this little test run.
谢谢各位参观这次试车
Nat…
娜妲莉
I'm going in.
我去了
But what can I say？
我还能说什么呢？
It's a Red Star day for me.
今天是我的红星之日
Then it's back to the day-to-day grind…
接着回去一如往常无聊的
of world domination and enslavement.
控制并奴役世界
Hi.
你好
（柯氏必胜）
Work your magic.
展现你的魔力吧
It's hot out there.
外面好热
It's hot in here too.
里面也好热
Maybe I can make you more comfortable.
也许我能让你舒服点
I've come undone.
我拉链没拉呢
That feels good.
真舒服
Thank you.
谢谢
I like what you've done with it.
我喜欢你的设计
Ours has bigger mirrors.
我们的后照镜比较大
I love cars.
我爱车
Do you like fast cars？
你喜欢快车吗？
I like fast everything.
只要是快的我都喜欢
Oh my God.
我的老天
Thanks for the ride.
谢谢你载我一程
You're welcome.
别客气
Mission accomplished.
任务完成
Tomorrow morning Corwin will give us a tour of Red Star.
姓柯的明天会带我们游览红星
Ride'em，cowboy。Make me proud.
冲啊 让我露脸吧
Nat！
娜妲莉
What's going on？
怎么回事？
We got a friend on the track.
跑道上有个朋友
That creep from Chinatown.
是那个唐人街来的怪人
Creepy Thin Man.
竹竿怪人
It's a round track。He's not going anywhere.
这是绕圈跑道 他出不去
She's going after him.
她在追他
The microcamera has allowed us to study Red Star's layout.
针孔摄影机让我们看到红星内部
The mainframe is right behind that door.
主机就在那扇门后
That's where my software would be but the security looks incredible.
我的软体就在那里 但安全措施看起来很严格
- Restricted access。-Fingerprint ID.
- 限级进入 - 指纹辨识
Retinal scanner.
视网膜扫描
Angels，break it down.
天使们 说明一下
Only two Red Star directors can access the mainframe.
只有两位红星董事能进入主机
To get throught the security system，they have to synchronize their entrance.
要进去 他们必须同步进入
A gelatin scanning plate takes exact fingerprints.
胶状扫描盘读取指纹
A laser accurate to .009 millimeters scans the retina.
精确度到0.009公厘的雷射光束扫描视网膜
It is accessible only through a monitored airless antechamber.
只能通过一个受严密监视的真空走廊到达目的地
There's only one way to get through undetected：Be invisible.
要摸进去只有一个办法 隐形起来
（测量器启动）
The floor is rigged with pressure sensitivity.
地板装有压力感测器
Any contact exceeding .25 seconds triggers the alarm.
接触超过0.25秒触发警报
Sounds impossible.
听起来很难
Sounds like fun.
听起来很有趣
（一号董事）
（二号董事）
Mein Siegenbock ist sexy！
我是性感小猫
They got the wrong address.
他们弄错地址了
You ready to whip them into shape，Alex？
准备好要整顿他们了？艾莉丝
You must be Miss Aarons。I'm Doris.
你一定是艾小姐 我是桃莉
Sorry about the confusion.
抱歉这么混乱
I had you scheduled for next week。I don't know what happened.
我排定你下周来此 不知怎么会这样
That's what I'm here to find out.
这是我来此的原因
You are the efficiency expert.
你是效率专家
Yes，
对
I am.
我是
Bitch.
贱人
I heard that.
我听见了
Your methodologies are antiquated and weak.
你们的方法老旧又无用
Your procedures of approval ensure that only the least radical ideas…
你们的核准程序 确保了只有最基本的想法
are rewarded.
得到奖赏
Meanwhile，your competition is innovating！
而你们的对手此时却在创新
You.
你
What was the last suggestion you made？
你上回做出的建议是什么？
To make the Coke machine free.
提供免费的可乐贩卖机
Why？
为什么？
Caffeine helps us program.
咖啡因有助我们设计程式
Perfect，smart…
完美 聪明
simple and logical.
简单又符合逻辑
What did your boss say？
你老板怎么说？
He said no.
他说不行
Question！
问题
Who builds this company's products？
公司产品是谁制造出来的？
You do.
是你们
Engineers do.
是工程师
Not managers.
不是经理人
They should be answering to you，not you to them！
他们该对你们负责 不是你们对他们负责
Who else has an idea like this man's Coke machine？
谁还有跟他类似的建议？
All right！Tell me.
很好 告诉我
Better yet…
更好的是…
can anyone show me？
能带我去看吗？
（不准进入）
It's not working.
行不通
There's only one way to get through undetected：Be invisible.
要摸进去只有一个办法 隐形起来
The floor is rigged with pressure sensitivity.
地板装有压力感测器
Any contact which exceeds .25 seconds will trigger the alarm.
接触超过0.25秒 就会触发警报
Thank you，sir.
谢谢你 先生
I hope you don't mind if we look around.
希望你不介意我们四处看看
So we have complete access to Red Star's computer.
我们已进入红星主机了
And they have no idea we can peek inside.
他们不知我们能窥伺里面
You guys are tremendous。Thanks.
你们真行 谢了
I need evidence of Knox Technologies software in the Red Star system.
我需要找到红星系统里 有诺氏科技软体的证据
- Where is it？-Bosley has it in the laptop.
- 资料在哪？-在老波的笔记型电脑里
It has a direct link to the Red Star mainframe.
它能直接连上红星的主机
Bosley？
老波？
Maybe we should be doing our own analysis.
也许我们该自己来分析
Surely Eric would be the best person to…
艾瑞当然是最佳人选
Our goal was to learn if Red Star had stolen your software.
我们的目标是了解 红星是否窃走你们的软体
It would be unethical to let you access their systems.
让你们进入它的系统并不道德
If we get proof，we'll tell you.
我们找到证据就会通知你们
That makes sense。That's cool。Right？
有道理 对吧？
Right，Viv？
对吧 小薇？
You know，Knox may not be out of danger yet.
诺也许尚未脱离危险呢
Smile。Don't panic the client.
微笑 别惊动客户
One of us should check security at his house.
我们该有人去他家做安检
Absolutely。I agree.
当然 我同意
- Everything all right？-Yeah。Nothing up here.
- 一切还好吧？- 还好，上面没什么
Wow，that was cool.
哇 好酷
Who's that Green Beret？
突击队员是谁？
My dad.
我爸
That's nice.
照片不错
That's the guy who killed him.
那个人杀了他
Yeah。They were in Army Intelligence together.
他们服役于军情单位
This was his best friend and he turned on him.
这人是他的至交 但却出卖他
I'm sorry.
我很难过
Thanks.
谢了
Why do you keep it？
你干嘛留着它？
To remind me：Be careful who you trust。Don't take any wooden nickels.
提醒我要小心朋友 别随便相信别人
What about you？Did you ever have parents？
你呢？你没有父母吗？
I mean… I know you have parents，but I mean…
我是说 你有父母 但是…
Where's your mom？
你母亲呢？
She died when I was 6，and I never met my father.
母亲早年过世 父亲则没见过
You never met your father？
没见过他？
Now you work for…
你现在为一个
a man you've never seen.
从未谋面的人工作
That's an interesting trend.
真有趣的倾向
That was smooth.
太滑了
Want to play Scrabble？
想玩拼字游戏吗？
Don't worry about it。I got somebody…
别担心 有人会清理
That's okay.
没关系
What are they called？You know…
他们叫什么来着？
So，okay.
好了
- This is a panic button。-Okay.
- 这是紧急按钮 - 好
If you just press it，then any one of us…
按下它 我们就有人…
whoever's closest，will be here if there's any problem.
最近的一个 就会来处理状况
Like that？Okay。Right now，that would be you.
像这样？好 现在就是你了
But you don't have a problem.
但你没出状况啊
Yeah，l do.
我有
I don't know…
我不知道
how to make chicken.
怎么烹调鸡肉
Scrabble？
拼字游戏？
Shake'N Bake？
裹粉鸡？
I'll shake，you bake？
我裹粉 你烹饪？
I want to shake.
我来裹粉吧
- Hey，Pete。-How's it going？
- 彼得 - 还好吧？
- Good。How are you？-Good。It's good to see you.
- 很好 你好吗？-很好 很高兴见到你
- You want your ticket？-All right！
- 想拿票吗？-好耶
- Thanks for giving me a chance。-I wanted to see you.
- 谢谢你给我这个机会 - 我想见你
- Really？-Yeah.
- 真的？-是啊
- You look great。-Thank you.
- 你真美 - 谢谢
I've thought a lot about us.
我想了很多我们之间的事
No，no，no。I know you have something to say
不… 我知道你有话要说
but I have something to say too.
但我也有话要说
I've been thinking a lot about you and me and，well，us.
我一直在想我们的事
And I know that we have these crazy lives，but I can't help it.
我知道我们很疯狂 但我不能自已
I love you.
我爱你
Searching Red Star mainframe for Knox Technologies software.
搜寻红星主机内有无诺氏软体
Software not detected.
查无所获
Coming.
来了
Hello.
你好
Trick-or-treat for UNlCEF.
为儿童募款
That's a very nice costume，young lady.
小姐 很不错的装扮
It glows in the dark.
它会在夜晚闪闪发亮
I hope you like to dance.
希望你喜欢跳舞
Are you kidding？I love to dance！
不会吧？我最爱跳舞了
You want to dance on-stage？
你想上台秀舞吗？
- Us？-Yes！-No，the stage is for the ladies.
- 我们？-好 - 不 女士才能上台
Oh，never mind。I'll just find a spot on the floor.
算了 我在舞池里跳吧
No，no，wait.
不 等等
This is Soul Train's highest honor.
这是这里最高的荣誉
I won't let you not go up there。Yeah，she'll go.
我不能让你不上台 她要上台
Really？I've always wanted to go up there！
真的？我一直都想上台秀呢
Have a great time.
好好秀吧
Okay。I'll be back.
好 我很快就回来
Ms。Wood，there are some lines that I never cross.
伍女士 有些界线我从来不跨越
Lines have never stopped me.
界线束缚不了我
It's 「Miss.」 And it's 「Vivian.」
我是小姐 叫我小薇
Okay。Miss Vivian.
好 小薇小姐
Okay，Miss Vivian。You're a pro.
小薇小姐 你是专家
I mean，you're not a pro，but you're an executive.
我是说 你是个管理专家
We must keep our relationship professional.
我们要保持专业的关系
May I？
我可以喝吗？
I'll get you a glass.
我帮你拿杯子
She's pretty great，isn't she？
她很棒 对吧？
I said，she's pretty great，right？
我说 她很棒 对吧？
You guys are in really good shape.
你们的身材可真好
Definitely。Definitely.
不错 不错
All right。The Robot！
好耶 机械舞
Go，white girl！Go，white girl！
加油 白种女孩 加油
That's old school，right？Definitely.
那是老式舞步吧？没错
I'm Pete。How are you？
我是彼得 你们好吗？
The Running Man！Look！
跑步舞 快看
Incredible！It was great！
了不起 真棒
I'm having so much fun！This is so exciting！
我好快乐 真令人兴奋
You know，I have to go number one.
我要去化妆室
Look…
听着
what I'm trying to say is…
我想说的是
will you marry me？
你愿意嫁给我吗？
Oh，no，baby！Baby？！
不 宝贝
Baby？！God，no.
宝贝？天啊 不
Damn you，Salazar.
该死 萨老大
Damn you，Salazar！
Cut！
卡
Was that over the top？It felt over the top.
太过火了吧？似乎太过火了
No。That is the best shot，the best scene，the best movie on the planet！
不 这镜头太棒了 是全片最棒的部份
Hi.
嗨
How was your day？Great.
今天还好吧？很好
You know how superheroes have these secret identities，where they…
你知道超级英雄都有秘密身分
No。No superheroes.
不 不提超级英雄
You're an action star.I get a lot of action.
你是动作派演员 我则出生入死
That is so lame.
这真蠢
Hey，girls，you having fun？
各位 玩得愉快吗？
I'm having so much fun I could just die.
我快乐的要死呢
Jason，I'm one-third of an elite crime-fighting team…
我是打击犯罪小组的一员
backed by an anonymous millionaire.
由不知名的百万富翁所支持
Yes，that's it.
对 就这样
What are you doing here？
你来这干嘛？
Perfect.
太棒了
Come on！Go！Hit it！
快 走吧
Murphy O'Meyer…
我受够了
that does it.
真是的
Who sent you？
谁派你来的？
Who？！
谁？
Woo… Woo…
伍… 伍…
- Who？-Woo…
- 谁？-伍…
- Vivian。-Spit it out！
- 薇安 - 说出来
Vivian Wood！
薇安·伍
You bitch.
贱人
I love a fire.
我喜欢火
Hey.
嗨
Oh，my God！You're hit！
天啊 你中枪了
No。I mean，the squibs hurt a bit when they go off，but I'm fine.
不 火药包炸开时是有点痛 但我没事
What happened to my trailer？
我的拖车怎么了？
I haven't been honest with you.
我没跟你说实话
Were you in there when that happened？Look at it.
你刚刚在里面？你看看它
I'm not a bikini waxer.
我不是除毛美容师
Bummer。I mean，that was kind of a turn-on.
真糟糕 我是说 那满令人兴奋的
I have to go.
我得走了
- Charlie？-Yeah.
- 是查理？-是的
I have to go，but will you call me tomorrow？
我得走了 明天打电话给我？
- Of course。-Great。Thanks.
- 当然 - 太好了 谢谢
Excuse me.
借过
You're bad.
你好坏
Guys，finally you warm up a bit.
你们终于有点人性了
Dylan？It's Nat。Vivian Wood is a fake and an all-around bitch.
狄纶？我是娜妲莉 薇安·伍有问题
Her assassin just paid me a visit。We gotta warn Knox.
她派杀手堵我 快警告诺
I'm at his house now.
我现在就在他家
You are？
你在？
You know what？
这样吧
Call Alex and meet me at the agency.
通知艾莉丝到总部碰头
Dylan！Shit.
狄纶 该死
Don't stand next to the window，it's not safe.
别站在窗旁 那不安全
Toga.
床单罩袍
Listen，I just found out that… Who's that？
听着 我刚发现… 是谁？
Working undercover？
在做秘密工作啊？
It's a full-service job.
我提供全套服务
I'll bet.
我想也是
I can see by your gown that you're unarmed.
看得出来你没带武器
Some maniac could just stroll in and blow you both to bits.
随便谁都能进来 干掉你们
Viv，you're obsessed。All work and no play makes Viv a dull girl.
小薇 你想太多了 小薇工作过度不懂情趣
I have to tie up some loose ends here，so take a seat.
我来这里是要解决事情 坐吧
Want some champagne？
想喝点香槟吗？
「Enemy.」
「敌人」
I know.
我知道
Sad news.
坏消息
Your girlfriends are dead.
你的朋友们都死了
And Corwin？
而柯呢？
I don't think it's gonna work out，you and me.
我不认为我们有未来
Which is a real bummer，since you，Dylan…
这真糟糕 狄纶
are a tomcat in the sack.
你在床上很够呛
Let me get this straight。You're a woman.
我直说吧 你是女人
Women have natural intuition.
女人天生有直觉
And you're a detective.
你也是个侦探
And you had no idea that this was going to happen？
你对这一切都没感觉？
- I knew。-She knew.
- 我就知道 - 她知道
And I know what'll happen next.
我还知道接下来会怎样
Tell her，baby.
告诉她吧 宝贝
All the Angels are going to heaven.
天使都是要上天堂的
And Bosley？
老波呢？
We'll keep him。We like him。And his computer too.
留着 我们喜欢他 还有他的电脑
He's special.
他很特别
Corwin had nothing to do with this.
姓柯的跟这一切无关
No。But I never really liked him.
无关 但我也没喜欢过他
- And the kidnapping was a setup。-Afraid so.
- 整个绑架案是假的 - 恐怕是的
And Red Star was a setup.
红星的事也是假的
You got it all figured out。Any other questions？
你全都清楚了 还有问题吗？
Why？
为什么？
Ask your boss.
问你老板吧
Charlie？
查理？
You're after Charlie.
你在堵查理
Charlie，Charlie，Charlie，Charlie.
查理 查理
They say that in death…
据说在死后
all life's questions are answered.
生命的问题就会得到答案
Will you let me know？
你会告诉我吗？
Let's go get Charlie.
去追查理吧
Come on.
走吧
Are you all right？
你还好吧？
- What's going on？-Something's going on.
- 怎么了？-出事了
Where's Dylan？
狄纶呢？
They say in death，all life's questions are answered.
据说在死后 生命的问题就会得到答案
Will you let me know？
你会告诉我吗？
What are we doing？House of Pancakes？Sizzler？
我们要去哪吃饭？薄饼之家？时时乐？
You are the cheapest man on the planet.
你还真小气
What did it look like？
看起来怎样？
Oh，I don't know。It was，like，all cool and stuff.
不知道 看起来… 棒透了
You've never seen a booby.
你又没看过真的胸部
- Have too。-Have not.
- 我看过很多胸部 - 没看过
- I've seen lots of boobies。-Yeah，right.
- 我看过很多胸部 - 是啊
A little help？
帮个忙吧？
Don't ask.
别问
Where's Knox？Is he okay？
诺呢？他还好吧？
Oh，he's great。He's the bad guy.
他很好 他是坏蛋
The kidnapping was a setup。He's behind it all.
绑架是假的 他是幕后主使
What？Why？
什么？为什么？
He wasn't exactly forthcoming when he shot me out the window.
他把我射出窗外时并没说穿
Bosley！
老波
He's safe！Knox already has him.
他很安全 艾瑞·诺抓走他了
Wait a minute.
等一等
Let me get this straight.
让我弄清楚点
Bosley's with the man…
老波跟那个
who tried to kill us。That's safe？
想杀我们的人一起 安全吗？
He won't kill Bosley until he kills Charlie.
他在杀查理前不会杀老波
Kills Charlie？
杀查理？
Oh，Jesus.
天啊
I don't know what his plan is，but I know that we can stop him.
我不知他有何计划 但我知道我们能阻止他
If Knox thinks we're dead，why blow up the agency？
如果诺认为我们死了 为何要炸掉总部？
Why does he want Charlie？
为何要杀查理？
We do know that he wanted us to break into Red Star.
他曾指使我们闯入红星
Imagine how dangerous this would be in the wrong hands.
想想这要是被误用会有多危险
Knox used us to access the mainframe not to get back his software
诺要我们进入红星的主机 不是要拿回他的软体
but for control of their global positioning satellites.
是要控制全球定位卫星
Knox's software can match Charlie's voice over the phone.
他的软体能辨认查理的声音
And use Red Star satellites to track him.
并运用红星的卫星找到他
But why would Knox go to so much trouble to find Charlie？
但诺为什么要堵查理？
That's the guy who killed him.
那个人杀了他
They were in Army Intelligence together.
他们服役于军情单位
His best friend turned on him.
他的至交出卖了他
Knox thinks Charlie killed his father.
诺以为查理杀了他父亲
So if he can intercept Charlie's call…
要是他能拦截查理的电话
He can locate him.
就能找到他
But Knox has to get Charlie on the phone first.
但他得先让查理打电话
- But the only one Charlie calls is… - Bosley.
- 查理只会打给一个人… - 老波
May I have some ice water，please？
给我来杯冰水吧？
Fly to me，Angels！Please come！
飞向我吧 天使们 快来吧
Please fly to me，Angels！
请飞向我吧 天使们
I had a long talk with a squirrel once.
我曾跟只松鼠聊过很久的天
Longer than I've talked to most humans.
我还没跟人说过那么多话呢
Hello？Hello？Hello out there.
有人吗？有人吗？外面有人吗？
Any sign of Bosley's laptop？
老波的电脑呢？
They must have taken it.
一定是他们拿走了
- We should check Knox's place。-Let's go.
- 去艾瑞·诺家查查 - 走吧
I'll drive.
我开车
Angels？！Angels，help me！
天使们？天使们 救我
Bosley？
老波？
Angels！
天使们
We begin our broadcast day！Come and get me，girls！
今天的广播节目开始了 来找我吧 天使们
If you can follow the sound of my voice，
要是你们听得到我的声音
then draw some triangles or something
那就设法
to get to this location and save me！
到这里来救我吧
Is there a way to trace him？
有办法找到他吗？
Even with our equipment，he'd have to be within 20 miles.
即使有设备 他也要在二十英里内才行
The place I'm in looks like Cher's bedroom.
我所在的地方 很像雪儿的房间
And it stinks.
还臭气熏天
Tell us where you are.
告诉我们你在哪里
It smells like the ocean.
空气中有海的味道
And if I look out the window，I see the ocean.
从窗户看出去 就能看到海
He could be anywhere this half of North America.
美国西北沿海都有可能
Jack…
杰克
tell them where I am.
告诉他们我在哪
What？
什么？
It's a Sitta pygmaea！
是侏儒西塔
A pygmy nuthatch！
一种侏儒雀
They only live in one place！
世上只有一个地方看得见
Carmel！
卡蜜尔
I can't tell you anything else，except…
我没其他的好说了 除了…
this feels like the first day of the last of my life.
我觉得我的生命所剩不多
Or the last day of the first of my life，or something.
或是我剩下生命不多了
I have a lighthouse，two hotels，seven manor houses…
找到一个灯塔 两间旅馆 七座庄园
one owned by the National Parks，one by Nick Xero Corporation…
一座属于国家公园 一座属于瑞诺艾公司
- Is that spelled with an 「X」 or a 「Z」？-「X.」
- 是艾还是爱？-艾
It's an anagram.
这是个字谜
Rearranged，it's 「Eric Knox.」
重组后就是艾瑞·诺
Scrabble freak.
拼字游戏狂
An old tunnel leads down to the shore.
有个旧地道通往海岸边
A sea approach is the best way to get in undetected。We'll need a boat.
由海路过去不会被察觉 我们需要一艘船
And a cover。We can't use the speedboat.
为了要有掩护 不能开快艇
Head to the marina.
去码头吧
Chad，does this thing go any faster？
这玩意能快一点吗？
We're in a hurry，and I could open it up if you let me drive.
我们在赶时间 如果你让我开的话 我会开快一点
I'm sorry，friend of Starfish。There's only one captain of this love boat.
但这艘爱之船只有一位船长
That captain is me…
船长就是我
the Chad.
查德
The Chad.
Chad，captain of the love boat.
查德 爱之船的船长
The Chad.
查德
We're kind of in a hurry.
我们在赶时间
I'm the Chad.
我是查德
Knox Technologies voice identification software download confirmed.
诺氏语音辨识软体下载成功
Red Star satellite network uplink confirmed.
红星卫星网路连结成功
Revenge is fun.
报仇真好玩
I have to say，Starfish，I am honored…
我得说 小海星 我很荣幸
honored that you've taken an interest in my work.
你对我的工作有兴趣
And I think you're very pretty.
而且我觉得你很漂亮小海星
Starfish？
小海星？
Where are you going？
你要去哪里？
Starfish，are you going swimming？Where are you going？
小海星 你要去游泳吗？你要去哪里？
Where are you going again？
你这次又要去哪里？
Starfish？
小海星？
Was it the Chad？
是查德的关系吗？
No！The Chad was great！
不 查德很棒
The Chad was great.
查德很棒
I'll tap the signal from the roof.
我去屋顶拦截讯号
- I'll deal with Knox。-I'll bring our Bosley back.
- 我对付诺 - 我去救老波
「I don't know how to make chicken.」
「我不会烹调鸡肉」
Jerk.
浑球
Dylan.
狄纶
Thank God you're alive.
感谢上帝你还活着
You know my better half.
你认得我的另一半
It figures I'd meet the perfect guy and he'd already have a perfect girl.
我老是遇到这种完美对象 是早就有完美伴侣的人
Hello，blondie.
你好 金发小妞
Her girlfriend's here.
她的朋友都来了
Jimmy，Paulie，go secure Bosley，would you？
阿吉 大力 去看住老波
Like now，now，now，now.
就是现在 快 快
Bos？
老波？
- Bosley？-Natalie？
- 老波？-娜妲莉？
Natalie，is that you？
娜妲莉 是你吗？
Behind this door.
我在这门后面
Bosley，I'm so happy to see you！
老波 我好高兴看到你
We're all here。I'll get you out.
我们都来了 我救你出来
Red wire.
红的
Blue wire.
蓝的
GPS phone tap.
搭上卫星定位系统了
Pygmy nuthatch.
侏儒雀
- I'm getting tickled。-Who's calling now？
- 我好痒 - 谁打来的？
- It's Pete！-Pete？
- 是彼得 - 彼得？
Hello？
喂？
Hi，Pete。How are you？
彼得 你好吗？
I'm good。You said you wanted me to call.
很好 你说过要我打电话的
I did want you to call。I mean，I do want you to call.
我是说过 我是认真的
Ask if he can call you back.
叫他等会再打
I'm so happy to hear from you.
我好高兴你打来
I wanted to talk。I like spending time with you.
我想跟你说话 我想跟你在一起
I'd like to see more of you，maybe in a continuous block.
我喜欢跟你在一起 我想跟你相处更久一点
I know。It's just been crazy this week at work.
我知道 我这星期工作太忙了
Watch your back！
小心背后
Use the sleeper.
赏他一腿
Never send a man to do a woman's job.
男人办事就是不牢靠
- Nice work，Natalie。-Thanks，Bosley.
- 做的好 娜妲莉 - 谢了 老波
Pete？Hi.
彼得？嗨
You know，under different circumstances…
换个时空
we'd have made a great couple.
我们会很速配的
Yeah，if you hadn't shot me out a window
是啊 若你没对我开枪
and tried to kill everyone I love…
又试图去杀我所爱的人
we could have had a chance.
我们可能还有机会
Can you keep a secret？
你能保守秘密吗？
I mean，you can't tell anyone.
不告诉任何人
That you're disgusting？
说你很恶心吗？
You have the fullest，sweetest…
你拥有一双我所吻过
most luscious…
最饱满甜蜜
lips I have ever…
最迷人的
kissed.
嘴唇
I just gotta take this call.
我得接这通电话
Nine o'clock，Charlie。Right on time.
九点整 查理 真准时
Enter。Come on.
输入 快啊
Mr。Bosley's phone，Eric Knox speaking.
这是老波的电话 我是艾瑞·诺
Mr.Knox？This is Charles Townsend.
诺先生？我是查理汤森
I'm delighted the Angels helped you。Are you in the office？
很高兴天使们帮上了忙 你在办公室吗？
Hang up，Charlie。He's almost got you.
挂断 查理 他快找到你了
We're all at the beach，having mimosas.Can you join us？
我们都在海边喝香槟呢 你能加入我们吗？
I'll take a rain check，Eric。Is Bosley there？
改天吧 老波在吗？
He went to the men's room。He'll be right back.
他去上洗手间 马上回来
No，wait。He's coming.
等等 他来了
Bosley？
老波？
Okay，here we go.
好了 开始吧
That's not him。Sorry.
那不是他 抱歉
Can you hold on one second longer？
你能再等一等吗？
Not a problem.
没问题
Pete？Can you hold on a second？
彼得？你稍能等一下吗？
Sure.
当然
I like him so much.
我好喜欢他
Hey，Bos.
老波
Bosley？
He's coming，sir.
他来了
Sorry，not him.
抱歉 不是他
Can I take a message？
需要留话吗？
Just tell him I called，as planned.
跟他说我打过电话来了
Gotcha.
逮到你了
Just one more sec.
再等一下
Is this a bad time？
是不是不方便？
You seem a little distracted.
你似乎有点分心
Is this the famous Charlie？
这是有名的查理吗？
No，this is Pete.
不 我是彼得
Hey！I like that guy！
我很喜欢他呢
That man's got a beautiful telephone voice.
那个人的声音很漂亮
That's one more daddy you'll never know.
那是另一个你永远不会认识的爹地了
Bad news.
坏消息
I have to leave.
我要走了
I gotta go torture and kill your boss.
我要去折磨并杀死你老板
Mikey，Jerry，
老麦 小杰
you guys like angel cake？
想吃天使蛋糕吗？
Do you know how hard it is to find a quality man in Los Angeles？
你知道在洛杉矶 好男人有多难找？
Don't take my lighter.
别碰我的打火机
Wait，wait，wait！I have something to tell you.
等等… 我有话要说
By the time this is over…
等这一切结束时
all of you will be facedown on the floor…
你们都将倒卧地上
and I'll moon-walk out of here.
我则会跳着舞离去
You're not listening to me.
你们没听我说
First，you're going to help me out of my chair.
首先 你要帮我离开椅子
Then I'll leapfrog over you…
接着 在我打断他鼻梁前
before I break his nose.
我会跳过你
Since my trusty lighter…
由于我可靠的打火机
isn't working，I'll do all this with my hands tied behind my back.
故障了 我只好 绑着双手行动了
Get her！
抓住她
King Kong palm.
金刚掌
Buddha on lotus.
佛祖坐莲
And that's kicking your ass.
那招是让你满地找牙
Alex！
艾莉丝
Thanks，Bos！
谢了 老波
Come on，we'll miss happy hour.
走吧 别错过好戏了
He's heading north，just past Paradise Cove！
他往北走 就在天堂湾那边
Oh，boy，they found him。That's Charlie's cabin.
他们找到了 那是查理的木屋
- You've seen it？-You've seen Charlie？
- 你看过？-你看过查理？
I am his trusted friend and employee.
我是他朋友兼员工
You've met Charlie？
你见过查理？
What do you mean，「met」？
什么叫「见过」？
You've seen him with your own eyes.
你亲眼看过他？
I saw his hand.
我看过他的手
It could have been anyone's hand.
那可能是任何人的手
Let's see if I can win the teddy bear！
看我能不能正中红心
Sorry，Charlie.
抱歉 查理
Get Dylan！The missile's making a round trip！
去叫狄纶 飞弹往回飞
Dylan！
狄纶
Let's go！
快走
Charlie.
查理
You guys，
各位
we're finally meeting Charlie.
我们终于要见到查理了
Do I look okay？
我看起来还好吧？
Should we knock？
该敲门吗？
Charlie？
查理？
Good morning，Angels.
早安 天使们
Sorry I couldn't stick around.
抱歉我没能留在那里
We're so happy you're okay，Charlie.
我们很高兴你没事
I'm just fine，Angels。Mission accomplished？
我很好 天使们 任务完成了？
I think the client was blown away.
我想这客户是完蛋了
Eric Knox was born John McCadden.
艾瑞·诺原名叫约翰·麦
It seems his life's mission was to bring me down.
他似乎一心只想毁了我
His dad was in my Army Intelligence unit，working as a double agent.
他父亲们隶属于我的军情单位 他是个双面谍
When he was discovered，the other side killed him.
身分暴露后 他被敌方杀了
I guess that's not the story Knox heard.
我猜诺听到的不是这个版本
Charlie，I've really enjoyed working on this assignment…
查理 我很高兴能参与这任务
and I eagerly anticipate returning to work.
我很渴望回去工作
Bosley's had one too many Buddhas.
老波喝太多酒了
He's definitely had a few.
他真的喝了不少
I have a team rebuilding the office.
我已请人重建总部
It'll be better than new when you get back.
你们回去时 那里会焕然一新
Thank you，Charlie.
谢谢你 查理
Is there any chance you'll be joining us，Charlie？
你有可能加入我们吗 查理？
I'd love to，Angels.
我很乐意 天使们
But I have some precious treasures to watch over.
但我更喜欢从远处凝望
Come on，Charlie，it'll be fun.
来嘛 查理 很好玩的
We're drinking from coconuts and Buddhas.
我们在喝椰子和佛祖酒呢
How will we ever know you truly exist…
我们怎么知道你真的存在
unless you come have a coconut with us？
除非你跟我们一起喝椰子酒
Faith，Angels。It's called faith.
信念 天使们 就是信念
To Charlie.
敬查理
Let me toast you ladies，with some ice cubes！
我用冰块敬你们吧
Safe！
安全上垒
I have to go。I'm so sorry.
我得走了 很抱歉
I should go。I really should.
我该走了 真的该走了
Let's see if I can win the teddy bear！
看我能不能正中红心
The Chad is great.
查德很棒
He's great。He's great.
他很棒 他很棒
The Chad is great。He's great.
查德很棒 他很棒
The Chad is great.
查德棒呆了
The Chad is stuck.
查德卡住了
I'm having helmet problems.
我的钢盔有问题
I'm having serious helmet problems.
我的钢盔问题很严重
Nice！
好耶